[{"answer": " Like you said. It worked", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " All the time", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " You'll be needing a few dollars for your extras, Won't you, Pop? You're three weeks behind on the last twent", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " You'll work", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " my friend does you favors, kid. You got to do a little one for him once in a while", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Let me explain you something, kid. Stooling is when you rat on your friends, on the guys you're with.  When my friend needs a favor, don't try to figure it out, just do it. Now go ahead, join the congregation", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Go ask him, why don't you ? Ask him yourself", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " One of these days", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Now you got me! It's a wonder I wasn't punchy by the time I was twelve. The rulers those Sisters used to whack me with!  They thought they could beat an education into meI foxed 'em", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " How would you've done it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What for", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I really don't know", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "She's off limits for bums like you. Leave her alone", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Not that free", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Who is he! my friend, you're so softhearted and sof", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I'm not trying to tell you he's Little Lord my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Shouldn't we care about everybody", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Isn't everybody part of everybody else", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I never met such a person. Not a spark of romance or sentiment or or human kindness in your whole body", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "And when things get in your way or people you just knock them aside get rid of Them is that your idea", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "He was looking at everybody the same way. Asking the same question", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " His racket", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " He just got a call from", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'd get over there, my friend. I'll take the little lady home", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "He don't, huh?  Well, he knows thirt", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " I got it. Hot off the press", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " But you're the one I want to tell what you said over my friend about keepin' silent when you know the score I'm guilty you hear me? I'm guilty... ", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't get it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Who says", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend what's happening to you", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Told him what", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " You... ", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Don't tell me don't tell me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " my friend yeah  yeah I fought my friend", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " You want to know something I would have taken my frien", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Looping right! I never swung wild. I was strictly a short puncher hooks over 'n under  who", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yeah, really", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I wish I knew", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What do you want me to do, my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Confused kid? First he crosses me in public and gets away with it and then the next joker, and pretty soon I'm just another fellow down here", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Then don't", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Ten cents a hundred pounds on everything that moves in and out. And you don't have to lift a finger. It'll be thre", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Absolutely nothing. You do nothing and you say nothing. You understand, don't you, kid", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Absolutely nothing. You do nothing and you say nothing. You understand, don't you, kid", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You don't mean you're thinking of testifying against", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's you who's being hurt. By keeping it inside you, like a poison. Sooner or later it's got to come out", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I don't want you to do anything. Let your conscience tell you what to do", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Is my friend in", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " No", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Get some fresh water", "docId": "onthewaterfront.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "my friend... my friend... ", "qsentId": 52}]